Eze Bernardine May

No 5 NSANS Lane,

Abai, Aba.

Phone: 07038065257

E-mail: demayous1@gmail.com

Objectives

I am a software developer with over two years of successful experience in web and desktop development. As a Front-End Developer, I want to be responsible producing high quality solutions for company customers; bringing deep understanding of Modern HTML, JavaScript, and CSS, and the software development life cycle; and strong ability to execute and implement standard software architecture patterns.

Technical Skills

- 1. Web: Proficient with HTML, CSS, SVG, Electron, Javascript, D3js and React
- 2. Desktop: Proficient with Electron.
- 3. Extensive knowledge of Linux and Windows operating systems.
- 4. Mobile: Fair knowledge of React Native.

Experience

March 2020 - till date. **EmBED** Front-end Project Lead (Web)

• Led the front-end team in building **EmBED**; an educational gamified learning platform project.

April 2019 - October 2019. Learnfatory Nigeria

Front-end Software Developer

- Led the front-end team in building **Alozie** app project; a software that formats a PDF document.
- Worked with a team of 10 in building Suregift; an app that makes the art of gifting simpler but richer.
- Maintained an excellent attendance record, consistently arriving to work on time.

Education

Nicheal Okpara University of Agriculture; Imudike. Bachelor of engineering.	2014 - 2019
Lizzy Secondary Schools	2011 - 2014
Divine International Schools	2008 - 2010
Model III Primary School	200 5 - 2007